In this video
喺呢條片
we'll learn the 3 basic steps on building apps
我哋會學整app嘅3個基本步驟
We call it 'ADD'
叫做 'ADD'
appearance, details, and debug
appearance, details 同埋 debug
Here
喺度呢
we'll use the simple YouTube Downloader app as an example
我哋就用個 YouTube Downloader app 做例子
First of all, we'll deal with the look
首先，我哋處理咗個樣先
That'll be handled in the layout section
呢度就係 layout 呢 part 做喇
You're very lucky
你好彩喇
coz you can download a ready-to-view template on Github
因為你可以喺 Github 度 download 個 template
If you wanna dig deep on how to do it
如果你想知詳細點整
feel free to watch the episode 2 and 3
可以睇 呢個系列嘅
Once you've designed the app's layout
整好個 layout 之後呢
you need to fill in the details
你就要塞啲嘢入個涵喇
In our YouTube Downloader app
喺我哋個 YouTube downloader app 度呢
there're 2 basic functions
有兩個 function
You can refer to episode 3 and 4
如果你想知 detail 點整呢
if you wanna know in-and-out how we do this
可以睇 第3 同 第4 條片
Throughout the process
喺整 app 嘅過程呢
you'll for sure encounter errors
肯定會有出錯嘅
That's the tedious part of debugging
呢個就係最麻煩嘅 debugging
That's episode 5 and 6
第5 第6 條片你就見到架喇
Finally
最後呢
you'll learn how to convert the finished script to an actual app
你會學埋點樣將個 script 轉成個 app